http://ultimatebass.com/privacy-policy/

HomePrivacy Policy
Introduction
This is UltimateBass.com
and this is our full Privacy Policy. We are dedicated to the protection of the personal information of all users of our website. If you have any questions please contact us.
Ultimate Bass, L.L.C. is “A community built by people who love to fish for people that love to fish”. Our mission is to promote the sport of competitive bass fishing, to foster our youth and teach them the skills of this great sport, and to support conservation and education efforts to ensure that bass fishing as a competitive sport is available to be passed down to future generations.
This policy is intended to help you understand what information we collect about you and how we use it. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
Our mailing address is:
Ultimate Bass
5422 Amber Circle
Benton, LA 71006
USA
Email: laurie@ultimatebass.com
Phone: (318) 347-7380
What Personal Data We Collect and Why We Collect It
1.1 Registration in our Community
When you register for an account in our community we ask you for a username, your email address, and a password. This information allows you to personalize your account preferences on the forum. We also ask subscribers to special publications for their emails in order to allow us to send them intended information from time to time. We will never sell or profit from your email beyond the intended purpose.
Member registration asks if you are at least 13 years of age. Our forum is based on an outdoor sport that attracts people of all ages. We do not allow a person to register unless they are at least 13 years of age. If at some point in time we or a staff member is made aware that a member had falsified their registration then the member in question may be asked to prove their age and thus their eligibility to be a member of this community.
If this becomes necessary the parents of said member will be involved and the information will only be reviewed to satisfy our requirements. A note will be made to verify that the member is in good standing or that their subscription has been canceled.
When a member cancels their account their personal information is removed from our database however the posts that they have made will continue to show their information and will remain in the forum.
1.2 Forms, Comments, Polls, Reviews
When you leave comments on the website we collect the data shown in the comments form, your IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment if you use the service.
When you fill out contact or other forms and input your information that information is retained for an appropriate amount of time to enable our staff to assist you with your question or comment and then deleted. If any part of the personal information is retained, express permission will be gained in advance.
Polls and reviews are available from time to time on our site both in the community and on the blog. If you chose to participate in a poll you are giving us your permission to retain the information provided in that poll indefinitely. The reviews and polls on our site are used to garner a greater understanding of our users so that we may provide services even better suited for our members.
Ultimate Bass sends out various newsletters and emails from time to time and to do this we use MailChimp and an opt-in list. You can find the MailChimp Privacy Policy here.
1.3 Members
By registering for an account on the Ultimate Bass Fishing Forums, you consent to contact from Ultimate Bass including, but not limited to, a quarterly membership distribution, an annual Industry Achievements report, regular ad-hoc news and updates, invitations to attend events or participate in projects, and administrative correspondence. You can always get in touch with us to discuss or change your notification preferences, although not all membership contacts are optional.
Please contact us with any notification preferences you may have.
1.4 Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
1.5 Charter Members and Sponsors
If you support us by becoming a Charter Member or a Forum Sponsor we will collect the following information from you:
Name
Address
Phone Number (if applicable)
Email Address
Date of Birth (if applicable)
Payment Information
If you make your payment online it is processed through PayPal and your payment information is not accessible to Ultimate Bass. If you would like to make yourself familiar with the PayPal Privacy Policy you can find it Here to see what additional information that they may collect or keep.
1.6 Cookies
Cookies are small text files that are transmitted to your hard drive by webservers. Because they only contain text they can not spread a virus or cause your system any harm.
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
1.7 Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, ads, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
1.8 Analytics
Ultimate Bass uses Google Analytics to collect visitor information in order to make our site a better place to visit for the people who spend time here. Learn more about Google Analytics and privacy.
If you want to opt-out of the Google Analytics tracking you can visit the “Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Addon“. Just visit this page and follow the directions.
1.9 Google Ads
Google AdSense is a convenient way for Ultimate Bass to earn a few pennies while you visit. They provide us with an avenue to select ads that will show on our site that will interest our visitors. These are some of the ads that you see on our site. These ads use cookies to save a few things in cookies. Some of the things that they save is how many times you have seen a specific ad, or which site you were on when you clicked on that same ad. These things help Google to know what ad to show you, and what ad to show on our site. You can click here for the Google AdSense Privacy Policy.
1.10 Amazon Influencer Recommendation Ads
The Amazon affiliate program allows us to use our account on Amazon to recommend products to our users that we think they would use. We know that Amazon is one of the best places online to purchase fishing products and we trust that when you order something that you are getting a quality product. We love that with Amazon you can rely on their no hassle return policy and because of this we feel comfortable recommending products from their site to you. Click here for the Amazon Privacy Notice.
Who we share your data with
2.1 Akismet Anti-Spam
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. Akismet Anti-Spam helps keep spam under control by filtering out spam comments–hundreds of millions, every day! Automattic provides the services for Akismet and their Privacy Notice is here.
2.2 MailChimp
We use MailChimp for our notification solution and thus we add your email to our list. We will not sell your email to any third party or send any notifications beyond that which are stated clearly in this privacy notice and your registration agreement.
Please contact us with any notification preferences you may have.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Please contact us with your request about this.
Additional information
5.1 How we protect your data
We take  the protection of your personal information very seriously. We carry out regular audits to ensure that personal information you provide us with is being protected as best as we possibly can.
Absolute security, confidentiality or anonymity over the internet is not a possibility at this time. You acknowledge and agree that Ultimate Bass shall not be responsible for any damages you may suffer as a result of the transmission of confidential or sensitive information over the Internet, and that all such communications will be at your own risk.
5.2 What data breach procedures we have in place
If in the event there were a data breach Ultimate Bass would make our members aware by the fastest method possible. Some of the procedures that we would take would be emailing members of our community, making a post in our community and sending out a special newsletter as soon as we were aware of such breach.
5.3 Disclaimer/Limitation Liability
We do not collect any information beyond that which you willingly input into our system. Please be aware of the information that  you enter into any form as at this time there is absolutely no way to be  100% secure on the internet. All communication via the internet are subject to interception and thus all interactions are at your own risk.
Search
Popular Articles
Fall Topwater Bass Fishing “The Zara Spook”
A favorite Spook retrieval technique among anglers is called walk …
The Ike Foundation® Announces 2020 College Scholarship Winners
May 18th, 2020, Pittsgrove, NJ. Mike and Becky Iaconelli, co-founders …
October 2020  (1)
August 2020  (2)
July 2020  (2)
June 2020  (2)
May 2020  (2)
April 2020  (1)
March 2020  (2)
February 2020  (4)
January 2020  (4)
June 2019  (4)
March 2019  (3)
February 2019  (8)
January 2019  (4)
December 2018  (1)
November 2018  (4)
October 2018  (4)
September 2018  (8)
August 2018  (4)
July 2018  (7)
June 2018  (10)
May 2018  (2)
April 2018  (92)
March 2018  (209)
February 2018  (136)
January 2018  (85)
December 2017  (4)
November 2017  (3)
October 2017  (4)
September 2017  (4)
August 2017  (6)
July 2017  (11)
June 2017  (10)
May 2017  (11)
April 2017  (3)
March 2017  (12)
February 2017  (11)
January 2017  (17)
December 2016  (1)
November 2016  (10)
October 2016  (11)
September 2016  (12)
August 2016  (10)
July 2016  (7)
June 2016  (23)
May 2016  (16)
April 2016  (10)
March 2016  (1)
February 2016  (4)
January 2016  (15)
December 2015  (9)
November 2015  (11)
October 2015  (5)
September 2015  (10)
August 2015  (5)
July 2015  (17)
June 2015  (11)
May 2015  (16)
April 2015  (9)
March 2015  (21)
February 2015  (18)
January 2015  (16)
December 2014  (9)
November 2014  (11)
October 2014  (6)
September 2014  (5)
August 2014  (8)
July 2014  (5)
June 2014  (5)
May 2014  (6)
April 2014  (10)
March 2014  (13)
February 2014  (22)
January 2014  (16)
December 2013  (4)
November 2013  (8)
October 2013  (12)
September 2013  (11)
August 2013  (38)
July 2013  (9)
June 2013  (15)
May 2013  (16)
April 2013  (21)
March 2013  (26)
February 2013  (27)
January 2013  (22)
December 2012  (14)
November 2012  (9)
October 2012  (15)
September 2012  (22)
August 2012  (41)
July 2012  (13)
June 2012  (28)
May 2012  (18)
April 2012  (20)
March 2012  (23)
February 2012  (40)
January 2012  (16)
December 2011  (20)
November 2011  (13)
October 2011  (13)
September 2011  (12)
August 2011  (22)
July 2011  (18)
June 2011  (23)
May 2011  (31)
April 2011  (36)
March 2011  (49)
February 2011  (34)
January 2011  (18)
December 2010  (6)
November 2010  (19)
October 2010  (30)
September 2010  (25)
August 2010  (23)
July 2010  (18)
June 2010  (44)
May 2010  (37)
April 2010  (40)
March 2010  (30)
February 2010  (18)
January 2010  (36)
December 2009  (13)
November 2009  (18)
October 2009  (39)
September 2009  (47)
August 2009  (26)
July 2009  (27)
June 2009  (36)
May 2009  (36)
April 2009  (52)
March 2009  (80)
February 2009  (61)
January 2009  (21)
December 2008  (19)
November 2008  (18)
October 2008  (2)
September 2008  (5)
August 2008  (6)
July 2008  (5)
June 2008  (17)
May 2008  (1)
April 2008  (5)
March 2008  (3)
February 2008  (14)
January 2008  (10)
December 2007  (1)
November 2007  (3)
October 2007  (23)
September 2007  (4)
August 2007  (2)
July 2007  (15)
June 2007  (15)
May 2007  (12)
April 2007  (6)
March 2007  (13)
February 2007  (22)
January 2007  (7)
December 2006  (8)
November 2006  (6)
October 2006  (10)
September 2006  (20)
August 2006  (18)
July 2006  (52)
June 2006  (9)
May 2006  (21)
April 2006  (17)
March 2006  (25)
February 2006  (21)
January 2006  (20)
December 2005  (29)
November 2005  (20)
October 2005  (22)
September 2005  (18)
August 2005  (12)
July 2005  (17)
June 2005  (20)
May 2005  (14)
April 2005  (15)
March 2005  (19)
February 2005  (14)
January 2005  (19)
December 2004  (11)
November 2004  (5)
October 2004  (19)
September 2004  (11)
August 2004  (37)
November 2003  (1)
August 2003  (1)
May 2003  (2)
Visit Us On:
